<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Causal-Italy</title><link>https://causalitaly.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Causal-Italy</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://causalitaly.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>CFP</title><link>https://causalitaly.github.io/docs/2021/cfp/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://causalitaly.github.io/docs/2021/cfp/</guid><description>Call for Papers # Causal-ITALY aims at bringing together researchers and practitioners in artificial intelligence, logic, and philosophy of science, for informal discussions and community building with a dedicated focus on methods and trends emerging from the study of causality.
This is in conjunction with the Italian Conference on Artificial Intelligence, AIxIA. For details on conference participation, registration, venue, please visit https://aixia2021.disco.unimib.it/ . We are currently envisaging a virtual format: further details will be announced closer to the event.</description></item><item><title>CFP</title><link>https://causalitaly.github.io/docs/last/cfp/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://causalitaly.github.io/docs/last/cfp/</guid><description>Call for Papers # Causal-ITALY aims at bringing together researchers and practitioners in artificial intelligence, logic, and philosophy of science, for informal discussions and community building with a dedicated focus on methods and trends emerging from the study of causality.
This is in conjunction with the Italian Conference on Artificial Intelligence, AIxIA. For details on conference participation, registration, venue, please visit https://aixia2022.uniud.it/ .
Submission deadline: 23rd September 2022, Anywhere on Earth</description></item><item><title>Organisation</title><link>https://causalitaly.github.io/docs/2021/pc/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://causalitaly.github.io/docs/2021/pc/</guid><description>Organisation # Chairs # Francesco Amigoni, PoliMI Federico Cerutti, UniBS Program Committee # Selene Arfini, University of Pavia, Italy Paolo Baldan, University of Padua, Italy Pietro Baroni, University of Brescia, Italy Marco Bernardo, University of Urbino, Italy Daniele Chiffi, Politecnico di Milano, Italy Luca Faes, University of Palermo, Italy Massimiliano Giacomin, University of Brescia, Italy Daniele Gorla, University La Sapienza, Italy Anthony Hunter, University College London, UK Claudio Mezzina, University of Urbino, Italy Paolo Milazzo, University of Pisa, Italy G.</description></item><item><title>Organisation</title><link>https://causalitaly.github.io/docs/last/pc/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://causalitaly.github.io/docs/last/pc/</guid><description> Organisation # Chairs # Francesco Amigoni, PoliMI Federico Cerutti, UniBS Letizia Tanca, PoliMI Program Committee # Selene Arfini, University of Pavia Pietro Baroni, University of Brescia Marco Bernardo, University of Urbino Luca Faes, University of Palermo Massimiliano Giacomin, University of Brescia Daniele Gorla, University of Roma Sapienza Claudio Antares Mezzina, University of Urbino Paolo Milazzo, University of Pisa G. Michele Pinna, University of Cagliari Mauro Vallati, University of Huddersfield Daniele Chiffi, Politecnico di Milano</description></item><item><title>Programme</title><link>https://causalitaly.github.io/docs/2021/programme/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://causalitaly.github.io/docs/2021/programme/</guid><description>The workshop will take place on Tuesday 30th November, between 09:00h CET and 13:00h CET. To join the event, please register and follow the instructions you find on https://aixia2021.disco.unimib.it/ .
Times are CET
09:00—09:05: Welcome
09:05—09:50: Sara Magliacane, Causality-inspired ML: what can causality do for ML? The domain adaptation case. Keynote
09:50—10:05: Andrea Duggento, Maria Guerrisi and Nicola Toschi, Nonlinear Granger causality from random recurrent neural networks
10:05—10:20: X. San Liang, Normalized causality analysis and causal graph reconstruction based on a rigorous formalism of information flow</description></item><item><title>Programme</title><link>https://causalitaly.github.io/docs/last/programme/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://causalitaly.github.io/docs/last/programme/</guid><description>TBD</description></item></channel></rss>