<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Causal-ITALY2022 on Causal-Italy</title><link>https://causalitaly.github.io/docs/last/</link><description>Recent content in Causal-ITALY2022 on Causal-Italy</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://causalitaly.github.io/docs/last/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>CFP</title><link>https://causalitaly.github.io/docs/last/cfp/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://causalitaly.github.io/docs/last/cfp/</guid><description>We regret to inform that Causal-ITALY 2022 will not take place. Apologies for any inconvenience caused. # Call for Papers # Causal-ITALY aims at bringing together researchers and practitioners in artificial intelligence, logic, and philosophy of science, for informal discussions and community building with a dedicated focus on methods and trends emerging from the study of causality.
This is in conjunction with the Italian Conference on Artificial Intelligence, AIxIA. For details on conference participation, registration, venue, please visit https://aixia2022.</description></item><item><title>Organisation</title><link>https://causalitaly.github.io/docs/last/pc/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://causalitaly.github.io/docs/last/pc/</guid><description> Organisation # Chairs # Francesco Amigoni, PoliMI Federico Cerutti, UniBS Letizia Tanca, PoliMI Program Committee # Selene Arfini, University of Pavia Pietro Baroni, University of Brescia Marco Bernardo, University of Urbino Luca Faes, University of Palermo Massimiliano Giacomin, University of Brescia Daniele Gorla, University of Roma Sapienza Claudio Antares Mezzina, University of Urbino Paolo Milazzo, University of Pisa G. Michele Pinna, University of Cagliari Mauro Vallati, University of Huddersfield Daniele Chiffi, Politecnico di Milano</description></item><item><title>Programme</title><link>https://causalitaly.github.io/docs/last/programme/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://causalitaly.github.io/docs/last/programme/</guid><description> We regret to inform that Causal-ITALY 2022 will not take place # Apologies for any inconvenience caused #</description></item></channel></rss>